Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
[water drips]
[woman breathes shakily]
[creepy music plays]
[dramatic orchestral crescendo]
[screams]
[ominous staticky music]
[camera flashbulb crackles]
[music abruptly ends]
Welcome. Creeper Nation.
I cannot wait to tell you
about today's mission.
Just know that it entails us
jumping off of a moving train.
Oh. yeah.
To help me give you
the rundown for all of this.
my charming.
very. very handsome Rick.
What is this?
I think we should explain
just a little bit
- what's gonna happen.
- What are we gonna find?
A masterpiece
of the one and only...
Don't tell them.
You have to watch.
You're not gonna want
to miss this one.
See you on the other side.
[Diane] Welcome to episode 27.
[rock music plays]
[indistinct chatter]
[elevator bell dings]
- Step one. sneak past security.
- Check.
[indistinct chatter]
We need all of our gear.
which will be with JD.
- Trash detail.
- He's trash detail.
[JD] Hello!
- [chuckles]
- [door opens. shuts]
Excuse me. ma'am.
This car is closed.
Sue me.
[hip hop music plays]
Nice meeting you.
What could go wrong?
Nothing. right?
- No. Let's go.
- [chuckles]
- [Vernon] Train!
- Run!
[train horn blaring]
[train rumbling]
[train whooshing fades]
[gate rattles]
- [gate rattles]
- [beeping]
Entrez-vous. s'il vous plaît.
[chuckles] Jackpot.
[ethereal music plays]
Oh. my God.
is that what I think it is?
- A Basquiat?
- [Rick] That's what they say.
Before his pieces sold
for millions.
when it was still just graffiti.
- [JD] This is priceless.
- Yeah.
Bet.
All right. guys.
you know the drill.
We document as much as we can
and then we get out.
- Look. but most importantly...
- Don't touch.
Vern. you're on.
Bro.
you ain't gotta tell me twice.
[camera shutter clicks]
Yo. yo. yo.
JD. that's not cool. man.
- What the hell are you doing?
- [Rick] JD. I told you.
Look. I don't even know
if this is real or not.
This could be our chance. Rick.
No. we don't touch.
That's the code.
Yeah. well. the code
can suck my dick.
Okay. come on. don't be a dick.
Just put that stuff away.
Let's go.
[grunts. chuckles]
That's what I'm talking about.
[Vernon]
Hey. hey. hey! Guys! Guys!
- Guys. stop! Hey! Hey!
- [Diane] Guys. stop it!
- [Vernon] Chill. man.
- Bitch.
[Rick] That's it. JD.
Get your shit and go.
You're gone.
This is not what we do. Go.
[metal clangs]
You know. I'd rather be rich
than one of you nobodies anyway.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
[walkie-talkies crackle]
Man: Over here!
Uh... Guys?
[suspenseful music plays]
[indistinct shouting]
[rock music and sound effects
play over speakers]
[Diane] Eighty-two.
Eighty-two thousand views?
- Holy shit. we're popping off.
- [Diane] Nope.
Eighty-two. Literally. just 82.
Wow. okay. I don't get it.
Like. what do we have to do
to make our channel slap?
- Porn Hub?
- Nope. I'm not showing my tits.
I don't know.
I think we're just irrelevant.
I have something
that might cheer you up.
Courtesy of Water and Power.
It's called The Paragon.
It's an old hotel
down the shore.
All right. so I did
a deep dive online.
Apparently. The Paragon
is where the legendary gangster.
Meyer Lansky. stashed
his missing 300 million.
Yo. that's a lot of money.
All right. apparently.
everyone that's gone
looking for this money.
never been heard from again.
Urban legend says
this is the place
where evil lives.
and it does not
take kindly to visitors.
Sounds... dangerous.
Man. think of all we could do
with 300 million.
That's what I'm saying.
I mean. if we happen to stumble
into that green.
not the end of the world
if we leave with some weight.
Look. guys. we either
have a code or we don't.
We document and that is it.
[sighs]
Before you get any ideas.
we go in as a team.
No more solo stunts
for the socials.
[scoffs]
Do I have your word?
- Yes. Yes.
- [chuckles]
- Okay.
- Good.
Actually. um...
I have a little surprise
for you. too.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh. Wow. It's... It's kind of...
kind of different.
Yeesh!
Different. Um. okay.
Well. that doesn't sound--
No. I meant different
in a good way.
You know.
like Lady Gaga different. right?
- [Diane] Right. right.
- [Rick] Diane. wait.
[sighs]
[notification chimes]
Wait. guys?
[gunshot sound effect plays]
What's up. bitches?
See this swag right here?
Yeah.
pretty sure that's Basquiat.
Never heard of this cat before.
but I know it's worth bank.
Also. just wanted
to give a quick shout-out
to my former crew.
What up. Creepers?
I know you're watching me.
And how's it feel to be a bunch
of broke-ass nobodies?
Yo. yo. yo. bossman Tod here.
Shaking shit up.
[indistinct chatter]
[gun cylinder spins. clicks]
- [gun clicks]
- [crew laughs]
Full psycho.
[crew laughing. cheering]
Traitor.
[indistinct chatter]
[chuckles softly]
[ominous music plays]
[birds squawking]
- [crickets chirping]
- [electrical buzzing]
[sighs]
Where's Diane?
She should be here by now.
Shouldn't you know
where your girlfriend is?
[toilet flushing]
Vernon?
- Seriously? Here?
- [Vernon] What?
[electrical buzzing]
[eerie music plays]
[Cora] And the pleasure cruise
continues.
Do not disrespect
my science. okay?
Look. yellow one gives me sweet.
sweet energy.
Red one helps
with my blood flow.
and it keeps my brain sharp.
And the green one. well.
the green one gives me
all the nutrients
that my body needs. okay?
[Cora] And what about those
purple ones. Vern?
There seems to be
a lot of purple ones.
[Vernon] Well. I mean. listen.
you can't spell healthcare
without THC.
- [clicks tongue]
- [Cora snorts] Oh. my God.
[keyboard clicks
and message sent]
- [knock on the door]
- Finally.
I think you got
the wrong room. buddy.
I don't. I'm with Vice.
- Vice. uh?
- It's the news outlet genius.
- Hi. Frank.
- [Frank] Are you Cora?
- You know this guy?
- Yeah.
He private messaged me. Come in.
[whistles]
That is a lot of equipment. Hmm?
Is that a bomb?
[chuckles] Okay.
Am I the only one
who's smelling bacon here.
or is it just me. or am I crazy?
I'm not a cop.
More like a vic--
Diane. perfect timing.
Who's the boomer?
[Frank]
My name is Frank Ballinger.
I'm with Vice News.
I'm here because I want to watch
you guys crack The Paragon.
How do you know
about The Paragon?
I saw Diane's post.
Like everyone else.
I'm sorry.
I said I was sorry.
Okay. we've all been talking
about how we need
to take our Instagram
to the next level.
Frank here
could help us do that.
- Hey. Vern. what do you think?
- I think he's a cop.
- Rick?
- No. absolutely not.
- It's a bad idea.
- [grunts] Diane.
I trust you. We're doing it.
[chuckles softly]
Okay.
[Frank] Nice van. huh?
Sadly. it didn't come
with a mystery-solving dog.
Hey. Cora. ask Rick if he
brought an extra can of diesel
like he was supposed to.
Wait. I thought
it was Vern's turn.
Absolutely not.
Cora told me that Diane said
it was your turn.
[sighs]
Or we could always take my ride.
[soft rock music plays]
This is absolute bullshit.
[sighs]
Honestly. I don't mind.
I'm pretty comfortable.
[tense music plays]
[car door closes]
[chain rattles]
[thunder rumbles]
AccuWeather never lies.
Okay. let's just make sure
we're out of the tunnels
before it hits.
Tunnels?
Aren't there any doors
or windows?
Boarded up and fenced off.
Ooh.
You want your story or not?
[thunder rumbles]
[sinister music plays]
This was JD's.
now it's the loaner.
[mysterious music plays]
- [exhales]
- Pretty glamorous hobby. huh?
I think I'll stick
to birdwatching.
It's really not that bad.
Except for certain situations.
Oh. yeah? Like what?
Oh. you know. I'm not really
into the whole
creepy-crawly things
that go bump in the night.
How far in do we have to go?
Should almost be there.
There's just one little thing.
And what's that?
That.
- [Rick] Really?
- [Diane] Yeah.
[tense music plays]
[crew members grunt]
[grunts]
Vern. is that smell you
or the tunnel? 'Cause it's bad.
Speak for yourself. bro.
I keep this body clean.
Wait. everyone hold on
for a second.
What is it?
Cora. sweetheart.
you're not gonna like this.
What is it?
[rats squeal]
Everybody. heads down. now!
[Cora yells] Oh. no!
[yells] Get them away!
Get them away!
[dramatic music fades]
[rats squealing fades]
[breathes heavily]
Cora. you all right?
[Cora] I hate rats.
[sighs]
[electricity crackling]
This is our way in.
There's gotta be
a different way.
I'm gonna go look.
Won't be long.
While she does that.
I'm gonna take a crack at it.
[chains rattle]
[all yell. gasp]
[Vernon] Holy shit!
[Rick] Could be their crew
was renovating
and was told to quit.
Or a barricade to stop someone
from getting in.
Either way. Diane. come back!
We found a way in!
[grunts]
[Rick grunts]
[Vernon grunts]
[Frank grunts]
[ominous music plays]
Wow.
Bet they had some badass parties
here back in the day.
Rick. you did it again.
[Diane] Hi. guys.
I'm so excited to have you
on this little journey with us.
This place is haunted.
[chuckles]
Jesus!
Say hi to my new best friend.
[chuckles]
[camera shutter clicks]
[cell phone chimes]
[ominous music plays]
[Rick] Okay. Here we go.
- [pigeons cooing]
- [Rick clears throat]
Ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to The Paragon. bitches.
The Paragon!
[wings fluttering]
[glass shattering]
[creaking metal]
Are you guys seeing this?
When do I move in? [chuckles]
This place is insane.
but there are rats.
Oh. yeah. and not the cute kind.
No. I'm talking the scary.
ferocious.
red-eyed kind of rats.
Yeah. didn't think
those existed. I saw them.
Wow.
Hello!
Fancy.
[chuckles] Oh. what a beauty.
You guys thinking
what I'm thinking?
Listen. I didn't take
those classes for nothing.
[chuckles]
[plays sinister piano notes]
- [cell phone ringing]
- I'm streaming. Rick. Decline.
[creaking]
Great. More rats.
[rattling]
Okay. maybe not rats.
Hey. whoever this is.
this isn't funny!
[pants]
[sinister music plays]
[grunts. pants]
[whimpers]
[dramatic stab]
God damn it.
She's not picking up.
Okay. you need to chill.
I'm sure she's fine
and will be playing a prank
on us any second.
All right.
but until we know for sure
we do this the right way.
we search room by room.
floor by floor.
Come on.
I...
Great. Dramatic.
- They had a fight.
- Over what?
Hair color.
What'd he say to her?
I don't think he would like me
talking with you about it.
Sounds complicated.
Uh. it's actually not.
You know. Rick wants a wife.
and Diane...
wants the world.
That's off the record.
So. Rick. is he in charge?
[Cora]
We let him think that he is.
He works security at Home Depot.
supplies us with most
of our equipment.
so the illusion
keeps us stocked with gear.
And I imagine that meets
with Diane's approval.
Oh. for sure.
I mean. she's got a firm grip
on the van.
as well as Rick's balls.
- What does Vernon do?
- Vern is our photographer.
He documents everything.
He's always taking photos.
- Somewhat to an annoyance.
- And you?
- Me?
- [Frank] Yeah.
Oh. well.
I'm the key.
So I open doors
when they're closed.
and I keep everybody honest.
Nice.
Thank you. by the way.
For what?
For helping me back there
in the sewer.
No problem.
So what's your wife's name?
Her name's Amanda.
Amanda?
You got a picture of her?
I do.
- She's a badass.
- [Frank] Right.
I like her ink.
Not what I expected for you.
Cora!
We're wasting time. Let's go.
[Cora] Thank you.
[camera shutter clicks]
[faint rattling]
[suspenseful music plays]
Diane?
[Vernon] Yo. guys.
Check this out.
Let's find Diane
and get out of here.
Do you want me to go
to the concierge desk
and see if I can find
a master key or something?
Good idea. Take a look.
Somebody should go with her.
Yeah. relax. big guy. I got it.
Come on. this way.
[hums]
Look. I'm just saying.
what could have made that?
A shadow.
A shadow?
You think a shadow made this?
Yeah. I don't really
know what you...
Wait. did you hear that?
What?
I don't know.
it just felt like...
[gags]
That's the claw. The claw is...
Really?
Cora. Cora.
- [gasps]
- [Vernon grunts]
- The claw.
- [Vernon] Yeah. yeah. yeah.
[Cora giggles]
Get up.
I saw you crushing on Mr. Vice.
Absolutely not.
Uh. no. no. no. hold on.
There was definitely
a vibe. okay?
What?
- I know a vibe when I see one.
- [Cora] Okay.
Well. the only vibe
I noticed was yours.
In the backseat of the car.
Aren't we looking for someone?
What's this?
"Paragon owner goes missing
after wife is murdered."
"Hotel set to close."
"Details have been kept
confidential by the police
due to
the ongoing investigation."
"However. it has been rumored
that the victim's chest
was found exposed
with her heart removed."
Wow.
Well. you really know
how to turn a girl on. Vern.
[camera shutter clicks]
How did you meet Diane?
In an abandoned mental hospital.
- [whistles]
- Kind of set the tone. I guess.
You reckon she's the one?
Look. I know you only
just met her.
but trust me.
there is no one that is like--
[groans]
- Get it off!
- [grunts]
[Rick grunts]
[pants]
- Hey! Hey! Get off of him!
- [Rick] Stop!
- [Vernon] Get off of him!
- [Frank grunts]
- Do not touch him!
- Calm down!
He's hurt! All right?
What kind of sick bastard
puts a bear trap in a hotel?
Oh. that's gonna need stitches.
Like a lot of them.
We've gotta make do
with what we got.
- [groans]
- [Frank] Okay.
Now. this is gonna sting.
Just a little.
[groans]
[pants]
[whimpers]
- [Frank] Come on.
- [Cora] Sorry. Sorry.
[Frank] That's it.
[pants]
Guys. I think we need
to take Rick to a hospital.
No. I'm not leaving without her.
It's Diane's phone.
She's upstairs.
Can you walk?
- Yeah.
- [Cora] Hey. hey.
I got you. Right. on this side.
Come on.
- Cora. get my camera.
- Let's go.
Come on. I got you.
[melodic music plays]
Yo. I think
this is our cue to bounce.
Cora. that's Diane's phone.
[Diane] Hey. whoever this is.
this isn't funny.
[grunts. pants]
[Cora] Oh. my God.
[rumbling]
[Vernon]
All right. so you guys know
I normally don't say this.
but we should call the cops.
Vernon is right.
We need to get real help.
Guys. look. we do not have time
to wait around
for the police. okay?
Agreed. We should keep moving.
Keep the noise down. all right?
Come on.
[rustling]
Hey. guys. what was that?
- [JD] Boo!
- [gasps]
Don't move! Get up! Get up!
Turn around!
[Vernon] What the hell. Frank?
You got a gun?
Man. I knew you were a cop!
- Missed you guys. too.
- JD?
- What. you know this guy?
- [Vernon] Watch out!
[all grunt]
- Come on. [chuckles]
- Don't touch me.
Move!
Come on. big guy. Up.
On your knees now.
Backpacks off.
Take the camera off. lady.
Come on.
Cell phones out.
Time for a little
social media detox. Creeps.
[tense music plays]
Where's Diane.
you piece of shit?
I don't know where your little
purple-haired skank is.
Probably off shooting
an OnlyFans video somewhere.
[Mack chuckles]
What I wanna know is.
where's the money?
I'm gonna ask you one more time.
where is Diane?
- Pardon me?
- Who are they?
They're The Scavengers.
They're the literal scum
of the Earth.
Oh. shit!
Tod. she always talks shit.
Just calm down.
Shut up!
You know. bullets are equal
opportunists. sweetheart.
Wow.
A white trash progressive.
You know. that... that is rare.
Figures. The chick is the one
with the biggest balls.
- Yeah.
- And mouth...
[Tod] You noticed that?
I noticed that.
What are we going to do
about that?
[Mack] Well...
I could think
of a couple of things.
It's funny.
I would still have more
than enough room to talk.
- Just shut up!
- Cut it out. man.
- Easy. No. Chill. chill.
- [indistinct murmuring]
It's okay.
Right? It's okay.
- [grunts]
[gun clicks]
We'll just take away her mouth.
Tod. you're taking it
too far. man.
I said shut up!
Hey.
You sure you know
how to use that thing?
[quivers]
[whimpers]
Okay. Rambo?
What. you do?
What are you. a cop?
No.
I'm just looking for my wife.
Frank.
what are you talking about?
Explain.
- Explain!
- [Frank] All right. all right.
[breathes heavily]
My wife is the reporter.
She went missing
a couple of months ago.
along with her photographer.
They were...
doing a story about the owner
of this hotel.
Cops? They've been no help.
I just couldn't find a way in.
As soon
as I saw your Paragon post.
I knew you guys found a way.
- [whimpers]
- Who gives a shit?
What's two less stupid bitches
in this world?
[whimpers]
[grunts]
Make that three.
- [spits]
- [grunts]
- [sniffles. breathes shakily]
- You stay right there.
That's just gross.
- That's Diane's!
- [grunts]
Oh. Oh. dude. this. Oh. yeah.
No. come here.
I didn't know. I didn't know
it was your girl's.
I didn't know.
Get up. take it.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
- Really. Take it.
- [pants]
Okay? Yeah? Good.
- No. Rick!
- Rick!
- [Tod grunts]
- [Rick screaming]
- [laughs]
[haunting music plays]
Rick! [groans]
[Cora] No. Rick.
Anyone else looking
for some frequent-flyer miles?
That's what I thought.
- Tod. this wasn't in the plan.
- Change of plans.
You said we were just
gonna scare them.
Now it's gonna be-- [groans]
Shut your mouth.
or I will shut it permanently.
- Come here. [grunts] Come here.
- [grunts] You're a psychopath.
I don't give a shit about
this Instagram bullshit.
- I'm in it for the money.
- Shit. yeah. bro.
And you know
where it is. all right?
Take me to the office.
Yeah. I can't do that.
[grunts]
- [Tod] What?
- [chuckles]
[spits]
That office is marked
on the blueprints.
And Rick.
he had the only copy. genius.
Yeah. okay. Okay.
[chuckles]
- Let's go find the skydiver. Go.
- [groans]
- Move.
- Easy. man.
Stop.
Rick!
[eerie music plays]
[laughs]
There's gotta be another way.
[chuckles]
Who wants to walk the plank?
I'll do it.
Aw.
Go.
[shouts] Go!
[grim music plays]
[grunts]
[pants]
[whistles]
[grunts]
[grunts. pants]
Bravo!
Rick. are you okay? Rick. talk--
Oh. my God! Oh. my God!
It's not him!
Hmm. Too bad. Let's go.
Wait. how am I supposed
to get back?
[gunshot]
- You don't! [laughs]
- [Mack snickers]
Toodle-oo. Come on.
[chuckles]
JD. this isn't you. man.
You gotta help us.
[faint moaning]
Diane?
- Go.
- [grunts]
Stay on him.
[door opening]
[door creaking]
[wind howling]
What's in there?
Narnia.
[sighs]
It's nothing. [gasps]
Oh. shit! [pants]
Please. Help me.
- Beth. Hey. hey. easy.
- [Beth sobs]
- It's okay. You're safe now.
- You know her?
Yeah.
She came here with my wife.
Beth. hey. hey. hey. hey.
where's Amanda?
[roof creaking]
[Beth] It's coming.
You're all gonna die. [sobs]
Down on your knees.
All of you. on your knees!
Come on!
Give me
the night vision goggles.
Come on. come on.
Shut the blinds.
[pants]
[goggles switching on]
- Mack. you see anything?
- [Mack] Nothing.
[Beth panting]
[pants]
[JD groans. chokes]
[Tod] JD?
[gasps]
What the...
- [creature snarls]
- [gasps]
- [creature growls]
- [gunshots firing]
- Mack. keep shooting!
- [creature snarling]
[pants]
Let's get out of here.
Come on now!
[somber music plays]
[inhales. breathes shakily]
Rick.
All right?
[groans]
[threatening music plays]
[grunts. pants]
[rattling]
Hello?
[gasps. pants]
[rattling continues]
[gasps] Oh. my god. Rick?
Oh. my god. Rick.
Oh. my God. Come on. I got you.
[grunts] Come on.
I got you. It's okay.
[both grunt]
[groans]
We're gonna
get you out of here. Come on.
No.
[roof creaks]
Hide.
[Rick panting softly]
[floorboards creaking]
[door creaks]
[suspenseful music plays]
[breathes heavily]
[weezes]
[gasps]
[creature growls lowly]
[sniffs]
- [growls]
- [grunts]
- [chokes]
[creature snarls]
[pants]
[chains rattling]
- [creature growling]
- [Cora yelps]
- [grunts]
- [creature growling]
- [electricity zaps]
- [creature snarling]
- [pants]
[sobs]
[pants]
- [electricity zaps]
- [light flickering]
[Cora panting]
What the...
What the hell? [pants]
[gasps]
Oh. my god. [pants]
Diane?
[sobs] Oh. my God. Diane.
[Tod grunts]
- [Mack] Nothing.
- [Tod] Come on!
- Come on!
- [Mack grunts]
[pants]
[static crackling]
[man] A powerful secret
has been shared with me.
A secret to become more.
Whoa!
[man] More than a foolish man.
Holy shit.
Whoa!
[laughs]
Let's go! [laughs]
[pants]
[man] What must be done.
must be done.
[Mack] Oh! Okay.
[man]
Rebecca will never understand.
[breathes heavily]
[man] Upon the digestion
of a mortal's sacred heart.
the chosen one shall be gifted
with supernatural strength.
Praised be the Dark One.
Come on. man.
let's just get out of here.
How about you quit
being a little bitch
and help me out with this. huh?
[pants]
- It ain't worth it. man!
- [Tod] Mack!
Mack! You're dead. Mack!
[pants. grunts]
- [gunshots firing]
- [screams]
[grunts]
[groans. chokes]
[man] What is gained in
eternity
will outweigh loss in this
life.
[chokes]
[Cora] Oh. my God. [pants]
[Tod breathes heavily] Okay.
[grunts. gasps]
- [creature snarls]
- [Tod grunts]
[grunts. breathes heavily]
[creature snarls]
[tense music plays]
[squelching and growling]
[intense music plays]
[gasps]
[breathes shakily]
[Diane] "The final
transformation from man to
beast
occurs when the Dark Lord
is offered the joining
of two souls desired
to be joined as one in...
eternal fire."
"Upon the ceremony.
the man-beast
will finally enjoy
everlasting life.
and all of the dark arts force
he hungers for."
I don't think so.
[door opens]
[gasps]
[snarls]
- [Cora] Vernon?
- [shushes]
Listen.
- [Cora] Vernon?
- Downstairs. Come on!
- Hold up.
- Whoa.
[wire twangs]
[Vernon gasps] Holy shit.
- [radio crackles]
- [Cora] Vern. you okay?
[breathes heavily]
- Hey. Yeah. we're okay.
- I can see you.
- [Vernon] Where are you?
- Upstairs. and I found Diane.
Cora. how do we get to you?
[intense music plays]
Get out. get out. get out!
It's coming!
Come on!
Come on. guys. Come on. come on.
- [Vernon grunts. pants]
- [Frank grunts]
[pants] Go find a knife.
Something sharp.
Anything. Go. go!
Hey. Cora!
Cora. we're in the kitchen.
We kind of need an exit.
Hey. Frank! Frank. I got it.
[Cora] Okay. I found an exit.
- Where is it?
- It's right in front of you.
- There. Go. go!
- Oh. you gotta be kidding me.
Oh. sweet Jesus. [pants]
[button clicks]
The motor's dead.
You're gonna have
to pull yourself up manually.
Get in.
What. you think this is safe?
[Frank] All right.
keep going. Radio.
All right. [grunts]
I should have told you guys
about my wife.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all good. man.
[breathes heavily]
[grunts]
Come on.
Vernon!
- Time's up!
- I'm going as fast as I can!
[grunts]
- [Cora] Oh. my God. Vern.
- [Vernon] Oh. fuck.
[Cora] Okay. Okay. okay.
[Frank grunts]
[banging on the door]
[grunts]
[grunts. groans]
- Frank. hurry!
- [grunts]
- [Cora] Come on. Frank!
- [Vernon] Come on. hurry up!
[Cora] Come on. Frank!
[grunts]
- [creature snarls]
- [grunts]
[metal clangs and crashes]
[pants]
[grunts. pants]
[Vernon] Come on!
[grunts]
- [creature snarls]
- [pants]
Vernon. get the knife!
- [grunts]
- [creature grunts]
[snarls]
Vernon! Cut the cable!
- [Vernon grunts]
- [Frank grunts]
[creature grunts]
[screams]
- [Vernon gasps]
- [Cora pants]
- Oh. my God. Frank.
- Give me the walkie.
- Frank. are you okay?
- [pants]
I'm fine.
That other thing? Not so much.
[Cora] Frank. meet us in the
penthouse.
Copy.
I just need a minute.
[both pant]
[melancholy music plays]
[sighs]
[Cora over radio] Frank?
We found someone
on the ninth floor.
[grunts]
[pants]
[eerie music plays]
[whimpers]
[gasps]
[kisses]
[eerie ambient music plays]
Frank.
Any sign of Rick?
I mean. he saved me. but...
We're gonna find Diane.
Yeah. she's right here.
Where is this?
[somber music plays]
[sighs]
All right.
I'm gonna go get Diane.
- Keep an eye on the monitor.
- [Vernon] Wait a minute.
[ominous music plays]
Oh. my God.
[door opens. closes]
[creature snarls]
[screams]
- [growls]
- [Frank pants]
[Diane pants]
[creature growls]
[Frank grunts]
[grunts]
[Diane sobs. pants]
[creature snarls]
[Diana screams]
Get your claws off of me!
- Let me go! [sobs]
- [growls]
[shouts]
[growls]
[pants]
[sombre music plays]
[sobs]
[Cora over radio] Frank?
Frank. did you find Diane?
Cora?
- Diane?
- Oh. thank God you're alive.
[Cora]
We thought that thing got you.
Is Frank with you?
He saved my life.
Hey. is Rick with you guys?
Time to get out
of this hellhole.
Um...
Diane. sweetheart...
About Rick...
Cora. where is Rick?
Diane. Rick is a hero.
He saved Cora. but...
[Diane] Cora?
Where's the last place
you saw Rick?
[Cora]
In a room on the third floor.
the end of the hall.
Rick?
Hey. Hey. hey. Oh. no.
Hey. Hey. Rick.
Rick. Rick. Rick. hey. Hey.
Please wake up.
Please wake up. [sniffles]
[sobs] Please. babe. please.
- [sobs] Rick! Rick!
- [Rick mutters softly]
- Are you okay?
- Diane?
- Are you okay? Oh. my God.
- [Rick] Yeah.
- Am I dreaming?
- I'll explain everything later.
[seagulls squawking]
[rock music plays]
A hundred million views.
Boom. baby. let's go!
I like that.
Listen. I have been saving this
for a very special occasion.
[chuckles]
Hey. guys.
I wish Frank was here.
To Frank.
- To Frank.
- [Vernon] Frank.
To Frank.
I have a surprise.
Oh. my God.
Wait. what?
Executive decision.
A little won't hurt the code.
My man.
[sinister music plays]
[eerie ambient music fades]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org